# Harsh Bakori

**Software Engineer** 

4 years of experience in Information Technology as Full stack developer. Strong working knowledge of all phases of software development life cycle like analysis, design, development, testing, configuration and maintenance of applications. Good problem-solving skills and working experience of agile by coordinating with teams at different locations.

Mo.:- 9427123617

Email:-

bakoriharsh5@gmail.com

Portfolio:-

harshbakori.github.io

**Recommendation:** 

**Cisco Letter** 

## **EXPERIENCE**

Software Engineer - Digantara

March 2023 - Present

Sr. Python Developer - Midocean Technologies

Feb 2022 - Feb 2023

Assistant Systems Engineer - Tata Consultancy Service

Oct 2019 - Feb 2022

#### **SKILLSET**

Operating Systems	Linux, Windows, Android / AWS & Digitalocean
Languages	JavaScript, NodeJS,Python, HTML, CSS3
Database	MongoDB, MySQL,MariaDB
DevOps Tools	Jinja, odoo project management, Electrum,
Other Tools	GIT, VSCode,Zoho,PYcharm ,Docker

# **Experience Details (Major Projects):**

(Below projects have been delivered in different forms some wear on site and others weare on Cloud like AWS/Digitalocean)

# 1. Voice assist with python

A Voice assistant enabled with windows system connects to google assistance and executes various tasks on windows machine.we can use cli interface just by speaking commands and it also connects with narrator giving full voice access to the system.

Developed in python and running on windows os, The program was also capable of connecting with IBM watson chatbot and other integrations.

Tools / Languages Python,Google Assistance ,IBM Watson	Tools / Languages	Python,Google Assistance ,IBM Watson
--	-------------------	--------------------------------------

## **SOFT SKILLS**

Team Work

Flexible / Adaptive

Ready to learn

Work Ethic

Critical Thinking

#### **EDUCATION**

Marwadi Education Foundation Group of Institution, Rajkot— Information Technology Engineering

2016 - 2020

JJ Mehta High School, Bilimora— HSC

2014 - 2016

LMP High School, Bilimora— SSC

2014s

## **LANGUAGES**

English

Hindi

Gujarati

# 2. ERP System modifications

ERP system modifications to enable various types of integration in odoo and Frappe ERPnext systems.

- connection with mobile app
- QR scanning and auto execution of actions on ERP system

Tools / Languages	NodeJS,Python,Frappe ERPnext,Odoo,Flutter

## 3. Sell Structure

Combination of frappe Node js and flutter mobile app to provide ability to track delivery and dealers point and transport insides

- track product shipping
- track and give record points to dealers
- Tracking of the inventory and transportation bills
- mobile application for same

Tools / Languages	NodeJS, Python, GIT, MariaDB ,Flutter
-------------------	---------------------------------------

## 4. Broker Portal

Trading account management portal for broker.brokers can login and see their client and modify according data for clients with telegram bot functionality.

- Telegram bot implementation with real time updates
- clients data modification in compliance with NSDL
- Esign functionality for clients and brokers
- Single portal multiple types of users with role and permissions management

Tools / Languages	Python, GIT , MariaDB ,Telegram Bot
-------------------	-------------------------------------